In the sentence above, we can see that there are two "can" words, but both of them have different meanings. Here the first "can" word is used for question formation. The second "can" word at the end of the sentence is used to represent a container that holds food or liquid.

Hence, from the examples above, we can see that language processing is not "deterministic" (the same language has the same interpretations), and something suitable to one person might not be suitable to another. Therefore, Natural Language Processing (NLP) has a non-deterministic approach. In other words, Natural Language Processing can be used to create a new intelligent system that can understand how humans understand and interpret language in different situations.
