It uses common sense reasoning for processing tasks. For instance, the freezing temperature can lead to death, or hot coffee can burn people's skin, along with other common sense reasoning tasks. However, this process can take much time, and it requires manual effort.

It uses large amounts of data and tries to derive conclusions from it. Statistical NLP uses machine learning algorithms to train NLP models. After successful training on large amounts of data, the trained model will have positive outcomes with deduction.
